brixton.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy

Brixton’s privacy and security measures are designed with the strictest security in mind, so any personal information that you provide to Brixton is used for the purpose of receiving Brixton communications and for personalizing and enhancing your web experience with Brixton. Brixton’s privacy policy is outlined below and tells you how we collect personal information, what information we collect, how we use it, to whom we will disclose it and how you can access, change and remove your information.

### HOW WE COLLECT THE INFORMATION

There are many ways that Brixton may obtain information from you: (1) via sign up on any Brixton website(s); (2) from an online, email, retail, fax or telephone purchase; (3) from navigational information about where visitors go on our website; (4) when you enter any Brixton sweepstakes/giveaways; (5) any time you submit a business reply, product, or warranty card; (6) when you sign up at a Brixton Store; (7) upon contacting customer service to request Brixton communications; and (8) upon signing up at an event. This information may be collected by Brixton or by vendors/service providers retained by Brixton and obligated to maintain your personal information in a confidential manner.

### THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you register on-line to receive our product information, you will need to provide us with your name, address and email address. When you make a purchase through Brixton’s website, you also will need to give us your telephone number and credit card number so we can process your payment and contact you in the event of any problems with delivery. If you contact our customer service department, you may need to provide us with additional information so that we can respond to your questions or concerns as completely and thoroughly as possible. In order to provide users and subscribers with the most efficient and enhanced service and to better understand your preferences, we may request your gender, year of birth, sports of interest, shopping preference and product interest. Whether or not you provide this information is entirely up to you. We also may collect additional non-personally identifiable information (for example, browser version, IP address) which will provide information regarding the general use of our website. The navigational information allows us to see which areas of our website are most visited and helps us improve the quality of your online experience by recognizing and delivering more of the most desired features and services.

### HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION

All personal information that we obtain about you will be recorded, used and protected by us in accordance with current data protection legislation and this privacy policy. By providing us with your personal information, you consent to us processing this personal information in one or more of the ways described in this privacy policy. We will primarily use your personal information to provide products and services to you, for example:

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature and to provide you with the relevant products or services (for instance to deliver a prize you may have won in a contest).
  * To send you information/materials via email or mail about products, offers and news we think could interest you. This information may relate to products, offers and news of Brixton. We only send you this if you have opted-in to receive Brixton catalogs or email messages.
  * To analyze visits to the website and learn about the interests of our visitors in the aggregate and to better understand your personal interests and needs, so we can improve our products and services and deliver to you the type of content, features and promotions that you are most interested in.
  * The information obtained from registration on-line is utilized to improve your web experience with Brixton by enabling you to obtain a faster checkout for purchases and/or opt-in to receive occasional emails, which provide you with the latest and greatest information regarding Brixton and its products.

The information we ask for when you order on-line is used only to complete the order, to confirm the order and to confirm shipment of the order. You may, upon placement of an order, opt to allow Brixton to save the information for a speedier checkout process the next time. This information is then stored only for the purposes of faster checkout and is not used for any other purpose.

### COOKIES

A cookie is a small removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer. Cookies are only used by Brixton to allow you to use Brixton’s website in the most efficient manner. Cookies allow you to place an order on our website and allow us to enhance and personalize your online surfing and shopping experience. For example, we use cookies to:

  * Remember the items in your shopping basket
  * Recognize you when you return to our website
  * Analyze visitor behavior

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Please note, however, that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our website. We also work with other companies who use tracking technologies, including web beacons, to serve ads on our behalf across the internet. These companies may collect non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our website about your interaction with our communications, including advertising and emails. If you object to web beacons, we recommend that you follow the instructions for deleting existing cookies and disabling future cookies. We will still know how many of our emails are opened and we will automatically receive your IP address, a unique identifier for your computer or other access device but we will not identify you as an individual.

### SHARING INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES

Brixton will never sell any information about you to anyone. We are part of a larger Company and we may share information with our parent and affiliated companies. We engage third parties to perform services in connection with the operation of our business. Examples of these services include payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, order fulfillment and shipping, marketing and promotional material distribution, website evaluation, data analysis and, where applicable, data cleansing. We may need to share personal information with these third parties so that they can perform these services, however, we limit the personal information that we give to them and authorize them to use this information only for the purpose of performing those services. In proceeding with your online order, you agree that both your name and address and those of the delivery name and address (if different) will be checked using third parties such as credit agencies. If you are providing a delivery name and address which is not your own you must have that person’s permission to give us their personal information and for us to use it for the purposes specified. By providing it you are saying you have their permission. We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our agents, including agencies or third party vendors so that they can provide marketing analysis and consult on advertising strategies. This information does not identify individual users. We also may share non-personal information, such as the number of users who visited the website during a specific time period or who purchased a specific product through the website, with our marketing partners, advertisers and others from time to time. This information generally is shared in an aggregated form. We may release personal information if we believe in good faith that: the law or legal process requires it; if we have been advised by counsel; we have received a valid administrative request from a law enforcement agency; or such release is necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Brixton, or any of our respective affiliates, business partners, customers or others. As with any business, it is possible that as our business develops, we might go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another Company, sale of all or a portion of our assets or buying online stores or other assets. In such transactions, information about customers will likely be transferred. You will be notified via a prominent notice on our site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. You will be deemed to have consented to the transfer of your personally identifiable information to any such successor entity unless you notify us via email to the contrary within the 30 day period. Personal information submitted to or collected through this website may be stored and/or processed in the United States, United Kingdom, Italy or Canada for the purposes described in this privacy policy. By using Brixton products and services (including our website), you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. We do not share, sell or rent to other third parties any personal information that you provide to us, except with your consent or as described in this Privacy Policy.

### EMAIL

Brixton has a Company policy not to flood people with email correspondence, but simply to give you periodic information so you can stay up to date on what Brixton is offering. Brixton will send emails to you only if you ask for them and you can easily unsubscribe at any time you want by calling our customer service department at (866)264-4245 or by following the instructions contained in the email. Brixton also uses your email address to confirm your order and to confirm shipment of your order and to respond to any inquiries you make on-line. All emails you receive will provide you with information as to how to get off the email mailing list if you so desire.

### DIRECT MAIL

If you would like to update your mailing information or want your name and address removed from Brixton’s direct mailing list you can give us a call at (866)264-4245.

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

If you are under 14, you should surf Brixton.com only with involvement of a parent or guardian. Although Brixton does not specifically direct its website, catalogs or emails to children, Brixton strives to provide children with as much customer service as possible without violating their privacy rights. For their protection, Brixton asks that anyone under 14 years of age not attempt to register with Brixton or otherwise provide Brixton with any personal information without the consent of a parent or legal guardian.

### ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Brixton will provide you with access to the personal information you provided to Brixton by allowing you to view, update or correct your information. In order to protect your privacy, Brixton takes steps to verify your identity before granting you access to the private information or enabling you to make corrections. Brixton will accomplish this through the use of passwords and personal data. If you want to find out what personal information Brixton holds about you, please contact our customer service department at (866) 264-4245. We may charge you a small fee for providing this information.

### SECURITY

Our website’s bunker security system is armed with a sentry system to monitor activity and prevent any unauthorized disclosure of credit card numbers or other personal information. In addition, we utilize a licensed system for credit card authorization and fraud detection. We use industry standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption to protect the confidentiality of your personal information.

### OPT OUT / UNSUBSCRIBE

You may request to stop receiving communications from Brixton at any time. You can choose to cancel emails only, snail mail only or both by calling our customer service department at (866) 264-4245. Also, all emails you receive will provide you with information as to how to get off the email mailing list if you so desire. It takes some time to put opt-outs in effect so you may still receive catalogs or emails from Brixton for several weeks after your request is received. You may also request to opt-out of Brixton retaining your personal data by calling our customer service department at (866) 264-4245.

### UPDATES TO PRIVACY INFORMATION

Please review the site periodically to see any updates to the information provided here. This privacy policy was last updated on May 25, 2018.
